{
  "quiz_name": "Adobe Target Business Practitioner",
  "quiz_breakdown":{
    "categories" : [{
        "name": null,
        "percentage_of_quiz_questions" : 0
    }]
  },

  "quiz_questions": [
    {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Adobe Target is a solution for optimizing personalization strategies across all digital channels; however, it currently doesn't support personalization efforts on mobile channels - True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Adobe Target - test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Adobe Target comes in offered in how many variations?","presented_options":["Standard and premium","Silver, Gold, and Platinum","Community Open Source Edition and Premium","Test and Target, Classic, and Premium"],"correct_options":["Standard and premium"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Adobe Target - test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Search and Promote features are only available with implementations of Adobe target Premium. True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Adobe Target - test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Capability of Adobe Target enables marketers to instantly target specific groups of site visitors with conditions based on concrete; real-time data?  Select correct answer","presented_options":["MultiVariate testing Segmentation","Site Search Optimizations","A/B Testing","Rules-based targeting"],"correct_options":["Rules-based targeting"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"What is Adobe Target - test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"There are many variable types of data we collect in order to get a 360 degree profile of a visitor that adapts to changing data in real time.  What are they? Select 5 correct answers","presented_options":["validation data; used for specific keywords and external identifiers","Behavioral data; what the visitor does, clicks, etc. while on digital owned property","Fundamental data: defined by the expressions that a visitor used on Facebook","Temporal data; when and how often a site is visited","Environmental data; device type, operating system, time zone, etc.","Referral data; where the visitor is coming from and what they clicked to arrive","Third-party and offline data; CRM, loyalty Programs, call center data, etc."],"correct_options":["Behavioral data; what the visitor does, clicks, etc. while on digital owned property","Temporal data; when and how often a site is visited","Environmental data; device type, operating system, time zone, etc.","Referral data; where the visitor is coming from and what they clicked to arrive","Third-party and offline data; CRM, loyalty Programs, call center data, etc."],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"What is Adobe Target - test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Capability of Adobe Target enables marketers to test multiple page elements, in more permutations than they can do manually.","presented_options":["A/B testing","Site Search optimizations","Multivariate testing","Recommendations and cross-selling segmentation"],"correct_options":["Multivariate testing"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Adobe Target - test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Capabilty of Adobe Target enables organizations to quickly compare two versions of content and experiences to determine the most effective content for distinct visitor Audiences?","presented_options":["Rules based targeting","Segmentation","A/B Testing","Mutlivariate Testing"],"correct_options":["A/B Testing"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Adobe Target - test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When individual data isn't available to determine a visitor's actual preference, what feature of the recommendations and cross-selling capability ensures that the visitor still receives content that may be relevant to them? Select correct answer","presented_options":["Targeted Facebook advertisements","Broad recommendations based on visitor segments","Language-specific Recommendation based on location","Indirect recommendations to all audience members"],"correct_options":["Broad recommendations based on visitor segments"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Recommendations and Cross Selling? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following familiar trusted, and proven recommendation strategies can be implemented using the recommendations and cross-selling capatiblity of Adobe Target Premium to promote relevant content and products?  Select three correct answers","presented_options":["Did you mean","Releated items","Customers also purchased","Site search auto correct","You may also need"],"correct_options":["Did you mean","Customers also purchased","You may also need"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Recommendations and Cross Selling? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following best describes the effectiveness of the decision engine of the automated personalization capability of Adobe Target?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["It works best on anonymous visitors for which no personal data is available","It is self-learning, so the longer it is active, the more accurate it becomes","It draws all its data from Adobe Analytics, so it is 100% accurate all the time","It is particularly effective on Secure pages, such as those used by financial services companies"],"correct_options":["It is self-learning, so the longer it is active, the more accurate it becomes"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Automated Personalization ? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are benefits organizations can expect to see after implementing Search and Promote to manage their site search optimizations?  Select the three correct answers","presented_options":["Increased Average Order Value","Increased customer behavioral data","Improved site speed and uptime","Improved customer loyalty","Increased conversions"],"correct_options":["Increased Average Order Value","Improved customer loyalty","Increased conversions"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Seach and Promote? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"_______ has built in logic that allows visitors' searches to be interpreted or corrected to deliver the right results.  Fill in the Blank","presented_options":["Search and Promote","Automated Personalization","Auto Search","Auto Allocate","Recommendations"],"correct_options":["Search and Promote"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Seach and Promote? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Using ________, marketers can set business and ranking rules that dynamically serve the most relevant search results to visitors based on customer data, and organizations can use metrics and KPI thresholds to set and trigger auomated merchandising rules.  Fill in the Blank","presented_options":["Search and Promote","Automated Personalization","Experience Targeting","Auto Targeting","Auto Allocate"],"correct_options":["Search and Promote"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Seach and Promote? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following page elements can be included in multivariate testing using Adobe Target?  Select four correct answers","presented_options":["Button colors","Hosting provider speed","Recommendations placement","Hero Image Size","Webpage URL","Banner variations"],"correct_options":["Button colors","Recommendations placement","Hero Image Size","Banner variations"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"What is Target Testing and Targeting? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"With ______ , organizations can see how one variation of a whole page, or just a page element, compares against another version.  Fill in the Blank","presented_options":["A/B Testing","Experience Testing","Auto Personalization","MVT Testing"],"correct_options":["A/B Testing"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Testing and Targeting? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"With A/B testing using adobe Target, organizations can quickly determine which versions of content and experiences visitors prefer, but winning content requires marketer intervention before the results are pushed to distinct visitor audiences.  True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"What is Target Testing and Targeting? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How many A/B or multivariate tests can you create and manage using Adobe Target?  Select correct answer","presented_options":["100","500","1000","100000","unlimited"],"correct_options":["unlimited"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"What is Target Testing and Targeting? Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following best describes Cross-channel optimization?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["It enables marketers to collate data from mulitple sources to create various audience segments","It allows marketers to target messages or app experiences based on the GPS location of the user","It enables mobile marketers to evaluate app experiences using A/B and multivariate testing","It allows marketers to collect data and target experiences across multiple devices and channels"],"correct_options":["It allows marketers to collect data and target experiences across multiple devices and channels"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Mobile App Optimization and Personalization.  Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following best describes Geolocation Targeting?  Select correct answer","presented_options":["It allows marketers to collect data and target experiences across multiple devices and channels","It enables marketersto collate data from mulitple sources to create various audience segments","It enables mobile marketers to evaluate app experiences using A/B and multivariate testing","It allows marketers to target messages or app experiences based on the GPS location of the user"],"correct_options":["It allows marketers to target messages or app experiences based on the GPS location of the user"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Mobile App Optimization and Personalization.  Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following best describes features of the mobile app optimization and personalization capabilities of Adobe Target?  Select three correct answers","presented_options":["Prioritization Testing","Audience Activaiton","Geolocation targeting","Media Optimization","Experience Targeting","Cross-Channel optimization"],"correct_options":["Geolocation targeting","Experience Targeting","Cross-Channel optimization"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Mobile App Optimization and Personalization.  Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following best describes Experience Targeting?  Select the Correct Answer","presented_options":["It allows marketers to collect app and web data across mulitple devices and channels","It allows marketers to target specific content, offers, or user experiences to a particular audience Segment","It enables mobile marketers to evaluate app experiences using A/B and multivariate testing","It enables marketers to collate data from multiple sources to create various audience segments"],"correct_options":["It allows marketers to target specific content, offers, or user experiences to a particular audience Segment"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Mobile App Optimization and Personalization.  Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following options are benefits of the mobile app optimization and personalization capabilities of Adobe Target?","presented_options":["Mareketers can test and target critical interactions throughout the user journey","Comprized data can be compared with that of rival companies","Customers who are satisifed with their app experience are more willing to try competitor offers","Customers can be delivered an efficient app experience that is tailored to them","Personalized app experiences are likely to decrease positive app store ratings"],"correct_options":["Mareketers can test and target critical interactions throughout the user journey","Customers can be delivered an efficient app experience that is tailored to them"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"What is Target Mobile App Optimization and Personalization.  Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Adding which URL Parameter to the end of the URL opens the browser's console to display messages that describe what happens behind the scenes and in which order?","presented_options":["?mboxDebug=1","?mboxTrace=1","?consoleWindow=1","?mboxWindow=console"],"correct_options":["?mboxDebug=1"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where is the 'disable#browser timeout#' flag set?","presented_options":["Visitor API","mbox Cookie",".htaccess","Adobe Marketing Cloud Debugger"],"correct_options":["mbox Cookie"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Before Debugging at.js using your browser's deveoper tools, what should you confirm is included in the page?","presented_options":["global-mbox","HTML doctype","Mbox Cookies","AT.js Javascript library"],"correct_options":["AT.js Javascript library"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When using the developer tools in your browser for troubleshooting, where would you go to view mbox contents and server calls?","presented_options":["Console","Timeline","Courses","Network"],"correct_options":["Network"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When you're using mboxTrace for Troubleshooting, which parameter prints to the console as a JSON String?","presented_options":["?mboxTrace=json","?mboxtTrace=console","?mboxTrace=string","?mboxTrace=print"],"correct_options":["?mboxTrace=json"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Counting Methodology is used to count visitors every 30 minute per browsing session?  Select correct answer","presented_options":["Impression","Activity Visits","Visitors","Visits"],"correct_options":["Visits"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When viewing MVT  Location Contribution Report, which table shows conversion rate, lift, and confidence for each offer?","presented_options":["Offer-Level","Influence","Summary","Primary"],"correct_options":["Offer-Level"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What information is displayed in the Confidence column? Select the correct answer?","presented_options":["Time Left until a winning experience triggers","Winning badge percentage calculator","Probability of the best conversion-rate","Probability of a winning experience within a 1% margin of error"],"correct_options":["Probability of the best conversion-rate"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"A4T cannot be used with the following types of Activites","presented_options":["Activities using Auto-Allocate","Recommendations","Search and Promote","Experience Activities","MVT Activities"],"correct_options":["Activities using Auto-Allocate","Recommendations","Search and Promote"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"When using the Traffic Estimator, what actions can you take to resolve the issue 'You have insufficient Traffic'?","presented_options":["Refresh the page","Decrease the duration","Increase the duration","Increase the number of locations","Reduce the number of combinations and locations"],"correct_options":["Increase the duration","Reduce the number of combinations and locations"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Where can you find a winner badge declaring a test activity winner?","presented_options":["Activity Result list in the status column","In Green box in header secion of activity","Activity / Reports Green Star in Experience column","Results Tab - under Winning Offer","Activity Tab in Experience Column"],"correct_options":["Activity Result list in the status column","In Green box in header secion of activity","Activity / Reports Green Star in Experience column"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Who can change the Target Standard role of a user? Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Target admin","Marketing Cloud User","Marketing Cloud Admin","Target Premium User"],"correct_options":["Marketing Cloud Admin"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What are the three user roles available in Target? Select three correct answers","presented_options":["Default","Admin","Observer","Editor","Super User","Approver"],"correct_options":["Observer","Editor","Approver"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This feature allows you to separate the reporting data by environment.  ","presented_options":["Host Management","Reporting Audiences","Reporting Environment","Reporting Groups","Environment Management"],"correct_options":["Host Management"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In Target Standard/Premium, what are host groups from Target Clasic called?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Locations","Domains","Host groups","Environments"],"correct_options":["Environments"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In the UI, where would you specify the default host group for reporting?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Hosts > Settings","Environment Properties","Hosts > Environments","Environment > Settings"],"correct_options":["Hosts > Settings"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you enable 'Show estimated lift in revenue', what will target ues to calculate the lift in revenue?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Average Order Value","Confidence Level","Revenue Per Visitor","Sum of Sales"],"correct_options":["Revenue Per Visitor"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"By default, how does Target generate CSS Selectors?  Select the correct ","presented_options":["Div tags","Class IDs","Section IDs","Element IDs"],"correct_options":["Element IDs"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"At which point will a user be able to create an Adobe ID in order to connect to the Marketing Cloud?  Select the two correct answers.","presented_options":["The Adobe IDs can be linked any time after accepting a Marketing Cloud Invitation","A Marketing Cloud Admin must configure the Adobe ID at the time of sending the invitation","After receiving a Marketing Cloud Invitation, but before accepting it","Before receiving a Marketing Cloud Invitation","After receiving a Marketing Cloud invitation, during the process of accepting it"],"correct_options":["Before receiving a Marketing Cloud Invitation","After receiving a Marketing Cloud invitation, during the process of accepting it"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is the process for linking your Target Classic account?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["User Permissions within Target Classic are configured for the Marketing Cloud","Marketing Cloud Admins can link it for each account","Target Classic Workflow permissions granted within the Marketing Cloud Admin Console","Target Classic user credentials can be added when launching the Target Classic Workflow"],"correct_options":["Target Classic user credentials can be added when launching the Target Classic Workflow"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where in the Marketing Cloud Interface can you set Target as the default landing page?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Adobe ID Account Settings > Custom Landing Page","Admin Console > User Preferences > Default Page","Edit Profile > Default Organization & Landing Page","Solution Switcher Widget > Preferences > Landing Page"],"correct_options":["Edit Profile > Default Organization & Landing Page"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What are the two tabs in the Adobe Marketing Cloud User Managent?","presented_options":["Active Users & Pending Invitation","Active User & Inactive Users","Current Users & Archived Users","Users & Admins"],"correct_options":["Active Users & Pending Invitation"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"New Users created in Target have which default role assigned to them ?","presented_options":["Standard","Observer","Editor","Approver","Admin"],"correct_options":["Observer"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which target role has the following capabilities - Can view activities, but cannot create or edit them?","presented_options":["Standard","Observer","Editor","Approver","Admin"],"correct_options":["Observer"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which target role has the following capabilities? Can create or edit the activites before they are live, but cannot approve the launch of an activity?","presented_options":["Standard","Observer","Editor","Approver","Admin"],"correct_options":["Editor"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which target role has the following capabilities? Can create, edit, activate or stop activiites?","presented_options":["Standard","Observer","Editor","Approver","Admin"],"correct_options":["Approver"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The activity delivery and the end user experience is different based on the enhanced vs non enhanced VEC modes.  True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This mode of the Visual Enhanced Composer will NOT work well for activity editing even if Target is not implemented on your site.","presented_options":["Non-Enhanced","VEC Enhanced","IO Enhanced","Server Side API","Enhanced Delivery"],"correct_options":["Non-Enhanced"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This mode of the Visual Enhanced Composer will still work well for activity editing even if Target is not implemented on your site.","presented_options":["VEC Enhanced","IO Enhanced","Server Side API","Enhanced Delivery","Non-Enhanced"],"correct_options":["VEC Enhanced"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The default configuration setting for VEC is set to what?","presented_options":["Non-Enhanced","VEC Enhanced","IO Enhanced","Server Side API","Enhanced Delivery"],"correct_options":["Non-Enhanced"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Visual Experience Composer settings can be found where in Target?","presented_options":["Setup > Preferences","Users > Preferences","Setup -> User Preference","Marketing Cloud > Target > Account Preferences","Marketing Cloud > Target > User Preferences"],"correct_options":["Setup > Preferences"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"VEC Modes - what are some common issues that can affect page peformance?   Select all that apply","presented_options":["No mbox is found on the page","Outdated browser version","Your site is using a proxy","Site does not allow itself to open in an iFrame","Target user does not have proper role assigned to support VEC Modes"],"correct_options":["No mbox is found on the page","Your site is using a proxy","Site does not allow itself to open in an iFrame"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Default Host groups in Adobe Target are : ","presented_options":["Localhost, QA, production","Development, QA, Production","Development, Staging, Production","Development, Production","Staging, Production"],"correct_options":["Development, Staging, Production"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Custom Host Groups can be created as needed in Adobe Target.   True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This type of list can be created that specifies hosts that are authorized to send mbox calls to Target.  ","presented_options":["white-list","black-list","host-list","authorized-list","mBox-enabled-list"],"correct_options":["white-list"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A _____ in Adobe Target is any web server(or web domain) from where you serve content or traffic has fired a server call to Target during any stage of your project.  Fill in the blank","presented_options":["Host","Client","Traffic Source","IO Integration Endpoint","IO Source"],"correct_options":["Host"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"These can be configured to serve both active and in-actitve Target Activities.  ","presented_options":["Environments","Hosts","MVT Tests","Auto Personalized Tests","New upcoming features in a Beta release"],"correct_options":["Environments"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Integrating Target with _____  enables delivery of assets (as part of activities) uploaded to the Adobe Experience Cloud assets folder. This integration enables access to all assets uploaded in _____  for delivery in Target activities.   Fill in the Blank.  ","presented_options":["Scene7","Imgur","Facebook","iCloud","Google Photos"],"correct_options":["Scene7"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Account Administration: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Adobe Target for mobile app comes pre-built.  Once you've downloaded it, you'll need to insert?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["RSID","App ID","Server","Unique Identifiers about your company(clientCode)"],"correct_options":["Unique Identifiers about your company(clientCode)"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When configuring a web implementation of Target without Tag Management, what funtion is used to pass parameters to the target-global-mbox?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["targetPageParams()","targetParams()","targetMboxParams()","targetGlobalParams()"],"correct_options":["targetPageParams()"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you're implementing tools above and beyond Adobe Target, such as Adobe Analytics, which of the following implementation methods would you use?  Select the correct Anwer","presented_options":["at.js","Without a TMS","Dyanmic Tag Manager(DTM)","mbox.js"],"correct_options":["Dynamic Tag Manager(DTM) or Adobe Launch"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This implementation option allows an external server to communicate directly with Adobe Target servers.  Select the correct asnwer","presented_options":["Adbox","Rawbox","At.js","Adobe Target API"],"correct_options":["Adobe Target API"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Under the mbox.js settings, which function describes the domain to set first party Cookies?  Select correct answer","presented_options":["mboxCookieDomain()","mboxCookiePageDomain()","mboxFirstPartyDomain()","mboxCookiePage()"],"correct_options":["mboxCookieDomain()"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What new option bypasses the need for an mbox around each area of content on your page?   Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Auto Create global mbox","Auto Create activity mbox","Auto wrap mbox elements","Target mbox elements"],"correct_options":["Auto Create global mbox"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When configuring the Adobe Mobile SDK, the 'Use HTTPS' option must be enabled to allow incoming connections via iOS10+ devices.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The web implementation of THIS does not use document.write().","presented_options":["AT.js","mBox.js","Server Side API","Adobe.IO","Experience Targeting","Auto Personalization"],"correct_options":["AT.js"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When Adobe Target is configured without Javascript or SDK Libraries, what happens when Target is completely down?  Select the correct asnwer","presented_options":["Visitors are shown a cached version of the content","an HTTP Error is given","Default content is displayed","Visitors do not see content, including default content"],"correct_options":["Visitors do not see content, including default content"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You can edit the Profile Lifetime value when modifying the at.js file.   True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"You want to implement without a TMS;  with the end result being an auto-created global mBox.  Which conditions do you need to take into account?  Select the two correct answers","presented_options":["Load the library fle asynchronously","Load the library file synchronously","Place library file in <head>","Place the library file in <body>"],"correct_options":["Load the library file synchronously","Place library file in <head>"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Under the X-Domain setting, which setting is used for both 1st and 3rd party cookies?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["disabled","x only","enabled","priority"],"correct_options":["enabled"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which page types are available when setting up a Recommendations Activty?  Select four correct answers","presented_options":["Landing Page","About Page","Cart Page","Home Page","Product Page"],"correct_options":["Landing Page","Cart Page","Home Page","Product Page"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Create an Activty: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you select two or more criteria during setup, how many designs can you select?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["1","2","unlimited","3"],"correct_options":["1"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Create an Activty: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Why must you select a page type?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["To Determine available metrics","To determine Available criteria","To determine available designs","To Determine available audiences"],"correct_options":["To determine Available criteria"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Create an Activty: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which options are available when you're adding a new recommendation to a page?  Select the three correct answers","presented_options":["Replace w/Recommendation","Insert Recommendation Before","Swap Recommendation","Insert Recommendation After"],"correct_options":["Replace w/Recommendation","Insert Recommendation Before","Insert Recommendation After"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Create an Activty: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are options when you're creating a recommendation?  Select three correct answers","presented_options":["Collection","Front Promotion","Custom Promotion","Back Promotion"],"correct_options":["Collection","Front Promotion","Back Promotion"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Create an Activty: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This type of Target Activity compares two or more versions of your Web site content to see which version best improves your conversions during a pre-specified test period. Select the correct answer","presented_options":["A/B Test","Auto-Allocate","Auto-Target","Multivariate Test","Experience Targeting"],"correct_options":["A/B Test"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following activities are only availabe with Target Premium?   Choose all that apply","presented_options":["Auto Allocate","Auto-Target","Experience Targeting","Automated Personalization","Recommendations"],"correct_options":["Auto-Target","Automated Personalization","Recommendations"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This Target activity delivers content to a specific audience based on a set of marketer-defined rules and criteria.  Choose the correct answer","presented_options":["Multivaritate test","Automated Personalization","Experience Targeting"],"correct_options":["Experience Targeting"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This Target Activity uses advanced machine learning to identify multiple high performing marketer-defined experiences, and serves the most tailored experience to each visitor based on their individual customer profile and the behavior of previous visitors with similar profiles, in order to personalize content and drive conversions.  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Multivaritate test","Automated Personalization","Experience Targeting","Recommendations","Auto-Target"],"correct_options":["Auto-Target"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This Target Activity identifies a winner among two or more experiences and automatically reallocates more traffic to the winner to increase conversions while the test continues to run and learn.","presented_options":["Multivaritate test","Automated Personalization","Experience Targeting","Auto-Allocate","Auto-Target"],"correct_options":["Auto-Allocate"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This Target Activity compares combinations of offers in elements on a page to determine which combination performs the best for a specific audience, and identifies which element most impacts the activity's success.  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Multivaritate test","Automated Personalization","Experience Targeting","Recommendations","Auto-Target"],"correct_options":["Multivaritate test"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The target Delivery Method used to support Native Apps: iOS & Android as well as Hybrid apps is","presented_options":["HTML / JS","React","Mobile SDK","Target API","Angular JS"],"correct_options":["Mobile SDK"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Target Delivery Method used to support the following Server-Server Delivery, Javascript restricted enivronnments and Internet connected devices is: ","presented_options":["HTML / JS","React","Mobile SDK","Server Side API","Angular JS"],"correct_options":["Server Side API"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Target Delivery Method used to support Web, Mobile Web and Single Page Apps(Angular, React, BackBone)","presented_options":["HTML / JS","React","Mobile SDK","Server Side API","Angular JS"],"correct_options":["HTML / JS"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The two library files available to support HTML/JS are: ","presented_options":["Target.js and A4T.js","Target.js and mbox.js","AT.js and Target.js","AT.js and mbox.js","AT.js and A4T.js"],"correct_options":["AT.js and mbox.js"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This library uses non-blocking calls and is more suited for Single Page Applications.","presented_options":["AT.js","mbox.js","Adobe.IO","React.js","Target.js"],"correct_options":["AT.js"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Targeted content can be sent back to the page, optionally including profile values for additional personalization.  True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Target Data is matched to analytics data throug which ID?","presented_options":["User ID","Cookie ID","SDID","Target ID","Experience ID"],"correct_options":["SDID"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The integration between Target, Analytics and Marekting Cloud is occuring where?  ","presented_options":["Server Side","On the client","In Batch Processes","Within Automated Scheduled Activities"],"correct_options":["Server Side"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"THIS combines Audience Manager, Campaign, Target and Analytics into a single package.   True or False","presented_options":["The Mobile SDK","Package Manager","Server Side API","AT.js","mbox.js"],"correct_options":["The Mobile SDK"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When using the Server Side API, the visual composer is the standard way to create experiences.   Tue or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Target Classic term 'Campaign' is referred to as this in Standard/Premium","presented_options":["Content","Campaign","Activities","Audiences"],"correct_options":["Activities"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Target Classic Term 'Offers' is referred to as this in Standard/Premium","presented_options":["mbox","Content","Activity","Experience","Offers"],"correct_options":["Content"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Target Classic Term 'Mboxes' is referred to as this in Standard/Premium","presented_options":["Pages","Tests","Activities","Experiences","PCD - Personalized Content Delivery"],"correct_options":["Pages"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Target Classic Term 'Segments' is referred to as this in Standard/Premium","presented_options":["Traits","Signals","Audiences","Personalized Groups"],"correct_options":["Audiences"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following is NOT an option to select as your default Landing page ? ","presented_options":["Feed","Assets","Exchange","Target","Recommendations"],"correct_options":["Recommendations"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"To manage Products, Users, Password Rules,  Tools & Support, you would go here.","presented_options":["Enterprise Dashboard","Adobe Management Utilities","Target Premium Dashboard","Experience Cloud Debugger","Target Standard Dashboard"],"correct_options":["Enterprise Dashboard"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you want to use targeting to display a different landing page for different visits, which activity type would you use?","presented_options":["Multivariate Test","Automated Personalization","A/B Test","Experience Targeting","Audience Targeting"],"correct_options":["Experience Targeting"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Target classic Term '1:1' is referred to as this in Standard/Preimum","presented_options":["Audience","Segment","Automated Personalization","Segmented Experience"],"correct_options":["Automated Personalization"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Adobe Target has individual Platforms for each delivery method.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"At which point will a user be able to create an Adobe ID in order to connect to the Marketing Cloud?  Select the two correct answers.","presented_options":["After receiving a Marketing Cloud invitataion, during the process of accepting it","A Marketing Cloud Admin must configure the Adobe ID at the time of sending the invitation","The Adobe IDs can be linked any time after accepting a Marketing Cloud Invitation","Before Receiving a Marketing Cloud Invitation","After receiving a Marketing Cloud Invitation, but before Accepting it"],"correct_options":["After receiving a Marketing Cloud invitataion, during the process of accepting it","Before Receiving a Marketing Cloud Invitation"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Adobe Target Allows for mobile app optimization.  True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is the process for linking your Target Classic account?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["User Permissions within Target Classic are configured for the Marketing Cloud","Marketing Cloud Admins can link it for each account","Target Classic Workflow permissions granted within the Marketing Cloud Admin Console","Target Classic user credentials can be added when launching the Target Classic Workflow"],"correct_options":["Target Classic user credentials can be added when launching the Target Classic Workflow"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What three assets are used to help Target decide which activities and experiences are returned to a visitor?  Select three correct answers","presented_options":["Ajax Request","mbox parameters","Profile Data","URL","HTTPS certificate"],"correct_options":["mbox parameters","Profile Data","URL"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When Adding new users to the Adobe Marketing Cloud, you are limited to adding how many products per user?","presented_options":["Not Limited","1","All Standard","3","4"],"correct_options":["Not Limited"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Activity Type does not allow you to use Adobe Analytics as a data source?  Selec correct answer","presented_options":["Automated Personalization","Recommendations","Multivariate Test","Experience Targeting"],"correct_options":["Automated Personalization"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Activity type compares all possible combinations of offers within your content areas to determine the most successful combination.  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Multivariate Test","A/B Test","A/B Test with Analytics","Experience Targeting"],"correct_options":["Multivariate Test"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Website Testing and Targeting Concepts - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Adobe Experience Manager comes with complete Target integrations out of the box.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Once the Global Mbox Request is received by Adobe Target, what gets executed first?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Profile Scripts","Content Scripts","Audience Scripts","DOM manipulation"],"correct_options":["Profile Scripts"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Adobe integration allows you to generate targeted emails?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Adobe Campaign","Adobe Audience Manager","Adobe Primetime","Adobe Social","Adobe Experience Manager"],"correct_options":["Adobe Campaign"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which phase of the Mbox process modifies the page content? Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Mbox Response","Mbox Delivery","Mbox Result","Mbox return"],"correct_options":["Mbox Response"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When a user triggers a page view and the mbox content is not cached, where do the Edge Clusters replicate the content?","presented_options":["Central Servers","Locally","Primary Servers","Edge Backup"],"correct_options":["Central Servers"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which phase of the Mbox Request/Repsonse Process is when a new visitor Cookie established?","presented_options":["Mbox Request","Mbox Response","Adobe Target Processing","Mbox Return"],"correct_options":["Adobe Target Processing"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Configured metrics are incremented during which phase of the Mobx Requeste/Response Process?","presented_options":["Mbox Request","Mbox Return","Mbox Response","Adobe Target Processing"],"correct_options":["Adobe Target Processing"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"With Adobe Target, the 1st party cookie is stored in the ______ of the requesting page? Fill in the blank","presented_options":["Clientdomain","Header","Footer","Head Section","mBox Parameters"],"correct_options":["Clientdomain"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If the browser rejects 3rd Party cookies, what will be displayed for all mboxes?","presented_options":["default content","no content","last content shown","random content for the activity","a warning to enable 3rd party cookies"],"correct_options":["default content"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You can use Adobe Analytics to report on Target data and use Adobe Aanalytics metrics features in Taget, if you select which integration option?","presented_options":["Adobe Analytics","Target Premium","Target Ehanced Analytics","Marketing Cloud Data Sharing","Audience Core Services"],"correct_options":["Adobe Analytics"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"If you use Analtytics as the reporting source for an activity, ALL reporting & segmentation for that activity is based on analytics data collection   True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Using the OOB integration provided for Adobe Target and AEM, users have full access to utilize all the Testing Activity Types from Target.  True of False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You should be able to target offers & experiences using Adobe Audience Manager  Segment data, when you choose to integrate?","presented_options":["Adobe Target with the Marketing Cloud","Adobe Target with Adobe.io","Adobe Audience Manager within A4T"],"correct_options":["Adobe Audience Manager with Adobe Target"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Tenchnical Architecture: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When does Experience Targeting evaluate visitors?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Each conversion","Browser specification","Device Type","Each Page Load"],"correct_options":["Each Page Load"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What Setting is required in the Goals & Setting page after  you cofigure your Audiences and Experiences?","presented_options":["Priority","Goal Metric","Objective","Reporting Source"],"correct_options":["Goal Metric"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which types of Activity tests are best used for testing multiple options for elements within a layout.","presented_options":["Multivariate Tests","A/B Tests","Experience Tests","Auto Allocate Tests","Auto Targeted Tests"],"correct_options":["Multivariate Tests"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When creating an A/B Test, using the Manual setting for Traffic Allocaiton splits traffic based on what assigned value? ","presented_options":["Performance","Success Metrics","Popularity","Percentage"],"correct_options":["Percentage"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What are the main fields when creating a profile script?  Select the correct answers","presented_options":["Code","Name","Conditions","Script","Description","Parameters"],"correct_options":["Name","Script","Description"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Mobile Targeting option allows you to target both phones and tables?","presented_options":["Is Mobile Device","Is Phablet","Is Mobile Service","Is Mobile"],"correct_options":["Is Mobile Device"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"***CHECK ON THIS *** Within the UI, what tab shows the influence of each element?","presented_options":["Location Contribution","Experience Performance","Experience Contribution","Locaiton Performance"],"correct_options":["Location Contribution"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What must your Reporting Source be set in order to access Audiences for Reporting?","presented_options":["Adobe Analytics","Adobe Target","Adobe Marketing Cloud","Adobe Audience Manager"],"correct_options":["Adobe Target"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"On the Goals & Settings page, what three options are available under the Priority Setting?","presented_options":["Highest, Tie-breaker, Lowest","1, 2, 3","Low, Medium, High","Low, Middle, High"],"correct_options":["Low, Medium, High"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How is the process for configuring a Target Activity to use Auto-Allocate different from other activity types?","presented_options":["When configuring metric settings, the primary KPI is designated to automatically allocate more traffic","Only Target Premium customers can choose Auto-Allocate as an Activty Type","Automated Personalization, is selected to automatically target visitors with the best experience","Auto-allocate to best experience is selected instead of the manual traffic Split"],"correct_options":["Auto-allocate to best experience is selected instead of the manual traffic Split"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following is not a benefit provided by Auto-Allocation?","presented_options":["Provides higher average campaign lift than a manual A/B test","Removes alogrithm-selection to ensure the benefit from the very best decistion the system could possibly take","Perserves the strictness of an A/B Test","Finds a statiscally significant winner faster than a manual A/B test"],"correct_options":["Removes alogrithm-selection to ensure the benefit from the very best decistion the system could possibly take"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"New Users created in Target have which default role assigned to them ?","presented_options":["100% of all Visitors","100% of Mobile Visitors","Not initially set","100% of Web Visitors"],"correct_options":["100% of all Visitors"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"At which stage of the activity creation process is the Auto-Allocate option designated?","presented_options":["Create","Target","URL Configuration","Goals & Settings"],"correct_options":["Target"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Create an Activity: Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What provides personalized content by using machine learning to sift through data and idenitfy patterns in visitor behavior?","presented_options":["Automated Personalization","Experience Testing","Multivariate Tests","Auto Target","Auto ML"],"correct_options":["Automated Personalization"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Pesonalization(OD) Auomated Personalization Concepts: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What are the new algorithms available for an activity in Automated Personalization  Select the correct answers","presented_options":["Lifetime Model","Random Tree","Lifetime Value","Faster Forest","Random Forest"],"correct_options":["Lifetime Value","Random Forest"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Pesonalization(OD) Auomated Personalization Concepts: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Legacy 1:1 customers who want to replicate the results of their 1:1 campaigns should choose which algorithm for optimization?","presented_options":["Lifetime Variance","Residual Variance","Random Forest","Legacy Variance"],"correct_options":["Residual Variance"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Pesonalization(OD) Auomated Personalization Concepts: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In which field do you enter an URL to create an Automated Personalization Activity within Adobe Target?","presented_options":["Enter Activity URL","Automate Activity URL","Personalize Activity URL","Assign Activity URL"],"correct_options":["Enter Activity URL"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Pesonalization(OD) Auomated Personalization Concepts: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What two inputs are combined to create accurate predictive experiences for site visitors?  Select the correct answers","presented_options":["Automated Experiences","User-Based Score","General Score","Bandit Score","Site Score"],"correct_options":["User-Based Score","General Score"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Pesonalization(OD) Auomated Personalization Concepts: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Automated Personalization allows you to preview Experience Combinations in which tool?","presented_options":["Visual Experience Composer","Marketing Cloud Debugger","Experience Cloud Debugger","Target Activity Validator","Preview Visual Composer(PVC)"],"correct_options":["Visual Experience Composer"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Pesonalization(OD) Auomated Personalization Concepts: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Automated Personalization Activities can be delivered via Rawbox/Adbox.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Automated Personalization is confined to the web-only via what Adobe Target Tool?","presented_options":["Visual Experience Editor","Visual Experience Creator","Visual Experience Composer","Activity Mode"],"correct_options":["Visual Experience Composer"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Algorithm is best used for sites with a high number of returning visitors?","presented_options":["Legacy","Lifetime Value","Random Forest","Legacy Value"],"correct_options":["Lifetime Value"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When Leveraging third party data into an Automated Personalization integration, you should be aware of potential impacts to page performance.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"To help Automated Personalization learn and adapt over time, what ongoing split is recommended for site traffic?  ","presented_options":["Multi-user Experience","Shared Experience","Mixed Experience","Random Experience"],"correct_options":["Random Experience"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which variables are used in the Legacy Residual Variance algorithm.  Select the correct answers","presented_options":["Top-10 nominal variables","All user Variables","Ten numerical input variables","Random Nominal variables","Top ten variable inputs"],"correct_options":["Top-10 nominal variables","Ten numerical input variables"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Automated Personalization follows the same request pattern as what server call interacation?  Select the correct anwers","presented_options":["Mbox parameters","MboxDefine/MboxUpdate","Recommendations Entity Feed","Mbox"],"correct_options":["Mbox parameters","Mbox"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What Javascript files are used by Automated Personalization?  Select the correct anwers","presented_options":["at.js","mbox.js","mbox-target.js","ap.js","profile.js"],"correct_options":["at.js","mbox.js"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Automated Personalization is based on visits?  True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Technical Architecture: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What percentage of your audience receives a random experience by default?","presented_options":["0.9","0.05","0.1","0"],"correct_options":["0.1"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Implementation Overview: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Is it possible to perform both A/B Actions and AP Actions inside of the Visual Experience Composer?  True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Implementation Overview: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which visit-based integration is not compatible with Automated Personalization?","presented_options":["Mbox parameters","Analytics as a data-source","Shared Audiences","Customer Attributes"],"correct_options":["Analytics as a data-source"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Implementation Overview: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Within the Automated Personalization UI, what variable is set in the Control?  Select correct answer","presented_options":["Experiences","Random Experiences","Goals"],"correct_options":["Random Experiences"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Implementation Overview: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Within The Visual Experience Composer's 'Change Text/HTML' option, you are only allowed to modify HTML & CSS.  True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Create an AP Activity TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"At which step in the activty creation process do you designate the algorithm your activity will use for machine learning?","presented_options":["Create","Logic","Goals & Settings","Target"],"correct_options":["Target"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Create an AP Activity TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What button would you click to combine objects into the same Report Group?","presented_options":["Content","Configure Combinations","Manage Content","Reporting"],"correct_options":["Content"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Create an AP Activity TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Metric does the Adobe target Automated Personalization algorithm optimize toward?","presented_options":["Success Goal","Conversion Metric","Primary Algorithm","Optimization Goal"],"correct_options":["Optimization Goal"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Create an AP Activity TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"To follow visitor behavior beyond the click, what setting do you disable to designate separate restart metric?","presented_options":["Follow Visitor","Restart Activity","Same as Optimization Goal","Conversion Metric"],"correct_options":["Same as Optimization Goal"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Create an AP Activity TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What option allows you to switch between Host Groups?","presented_options":["Settings","Preferences","Options","Content"],"correct_options":["Settings"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Personalization Reporting TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What Report type allows you to check individual asset performance?","presented_options":["Content Report","Offer Report","Detailed view Report","Asset Report"],"correct_options":["Offer Report"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Personalization Reporting TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is a control group within Automated Personalization?","presented_options":["Default Content","Targeted Content delivery Default Content","Random experiences served to visitors","Cached content served to visitors"],"correct_options":["Random experiences served to visitors"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Personalization Reporting TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"With the Offer report group selected, what continued report is displayed when selecting an individual asset?","presented_options":["Predictive Variables Report","Varible highlight Report","Deep Dive Report","Visitor Report"],"correct_options":["Predictive Variables Report"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Personalization Reporting TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"By Default, which Audience type is shown for Automated Personalization?","presented_options":["Google SERP Visitors","All Qualified Visitors","Recent Visitors","Frequent Visitors"],"correct_options":["All Qualified Visitors"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Automated Personalization(OD) Personalization Reporting TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"After you send your team a QA link from your experience, you realize you are seeing another experience, rather than the recommendation you are expecting.  What is a possible cause?","presented_options":["\"Show default content for all other activities\" is enabled","\"Show default content for all other activities\" is disabled","\"Match Audience rule to experience\" is disabled","\"Match Audience rule to experience\" is enabled"],"correct_options":["\"Show default content for all other activities\" is disabled"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content - Perform QA & Activate a Recommendation : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How do you access Activity QA URLs?","presented_options":["Under the Overview Tab","Under Settings in Target","Under the Recommendations Tab","Under th Reports Tab"],"correct_options":["Under the Overview Tab"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content - Perform QA & Activate a Recommendation : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"To whom are preview links for?","presented_options":["All Editors","All Approvers","Activity Creator","All users"],"correct_options":["All users"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content - Perform QA & Activate a Recommendation : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If the option to match audience rules to see experience is enabled, what is required for the tester to see the experience?","presented_options":["The tester must click on the link","The tester must match the audience","The tester will see the link no matter what","The tester must ensure there are no collisions"],"correct_options":["The tester must match the audience"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content - Perform QA & Activate a Recommendation : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If no changes are made to an activity, when will the activity link expire?","presented_options":["1 Day","1 Month","1 Week","Never"],"correct_options":["Never"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content - Perform QA & Activate a Recommendation : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"if 'show default content for all other activities' is disabled, what are some things to keep in mind?","presented_options":["Collisions could affect which experiences you see","Default content will not be shown","Metrics will be incremented","Normal Priority rules apply"],"correct_options":["Default content will not be shown"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content - Perform QA & Activate a Recommendation : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which format is available for downloading Target data?","presented_options":["CSV","Tab","PDF","Excel"],"correct_options":["CSV"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Target Recommendations: Manage Activities: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which option is no longer available under the gear icon?","presented_options":["Counting Methodology","Environment","Metric","Control"],"correct_options":["Metric"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Target Recommendations: Manage Activities: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How do you change the default report?","presented_options":["It's not possible","Click the gear icon","It happens when you setup the activity","Click the three buttons above the Report Metric"],"correct_options":["Click the three buttons above the Report Metric"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Target Recommendations: Manage Activities: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What does Reset Report Data do?","presented_options":["Removes old data","Removes current visitors from the activity","Pauses the activity","Deactivates the activity"],"correct_options":["Removes old data"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Target Recommendations: Manage Activities: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When does a user qualiy for reporting in Adobe Target?","presented_options":["It depends on the settings","When Qualifying for an activity","On successfully triggering a metric","It depnds on metrics"],"correct_options":["When Qualifying for an activity"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Target Recommendations: Manage Activities: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which metrics are available by default for each experience? Select the correct answers","presented_options":["Lift","Revenue","Orders","Confidence","Pages"],"correct_options":["Lift","Orders","Confidence"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Target Recommendations: Manage Activities: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How many audiences are in reporting by default?","presented_options":["1","5","10","2"],"correct_options":["1"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Target Recommendations: Manage Activities: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How many reporting presets can you set up?","presented_options":["1","5","10","2"],"correct_options":["10"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Target Recommendations: Manage Activities: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What are collections eligible for?","presented_options":["Feeds","A/B Tests","Exclustions","Recommendations"],"correct_options":["Recommendations"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is the main purpose of collections?","presented_options":["To organize products","To Exclude products","To Add entity information","To Remove Products"],"correct_options":["To organize products"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How many total collections can you create?","presented_options":["100","25","Unlimited","10"],"correct_options":["Unlimited"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How can you create a collection within Recommendations?","presented_options":["Within a feed","In an Audience","Using Advanced Search","In an Activity"],"correct_options":["Using Advanced Search"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How many products can you add to each collection?","presented_options":["25","10","Unlimited","100"],"correct_options":["Unlimited"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which frequency options are available for Feeds?","presented_options":["Every 2 weeks","Monthly","Weekly","Daily"],"correct_options":["Every 2 weeks","Weekly","Daily"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Data Feeds and Settings: TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which feed type requires no mapping during initial setup?","presented_options":["SQL","Analytics Classification","Google Product Feed","CSV"],"correct_options":["CSV"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which feed types require an FTP or URL Location?","presented_options":["CSV","Google Product Feed","Analytics Classification"],"correct_options":["CSV","Google Product Feed"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is another way to get feed information to Recommendations?","presented_options":["mBox","Exlcusions","Criteria","Collections"],"correct_options":["mBox"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is Adobe's proprietary method for uploading a feed?","presented_options":["CSV","Analytics Classification","API","Google"],"correct_options":["CSV"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are available options when you're setting up a Recommendations feed?","presented_options":["SQL","CSV","Manual","Google Product Feed","Analytics Classification"],"correct_options":["CSV","Google Product Feed","Analytics Classification"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target: Target Recommendations: Personalized Dynamic Content (OD) Collections, exclusions and catalog search : TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"There is NOT an immediate execution of Javascript in Target Responses, when using which library?","presented_options":["mbox.js","target.js","async.js","React.js"],"correct_options":["AT.js"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In Adobe Target Modify AT.js settings, 'Client Code' refers to which of the following:","presented_options":["target code running in client browsers","customizable code to execute within mBox","Unique code given for your company's target account"],"correct_options":["Unique code given for your company's target account"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Profile lifetime, refers to how long Visitor Profiles are stored on Adobe Target.  The default timeframe is set to:","presented_options":["24 hours","1 week","2 weeks","1 month","1 year"],"correct_options":["2 weeks"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Under the X-Domain setting, which setting is used for 3rd party cookies only?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["disabled","x only","enabled","priority"],"correct_options":["x only"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Under the X-Domain setting, which setting is used for 1st party cookies only?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["disabled","x only","enabled","priority"],"correct_options":["disabled"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When using AT.js or mbox.js, what occurs for a given user if the default timeout value is reached?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Target will continue to make the mbox request and will display the response once it becomes available","Target will exclude that visitor from making any mbox calls for the next 30 minutes and will serve only default content during that timeframe","Target will display default content for that mbox and will continue to make subsequent mbox calls to deliver a personalized experience","Target will not show any content for the mbox call"],"correct_options":["Target will exclude that visitor from making any mbox calls for the next 30 minutes and will serve only default content during that timeframe"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In the Modify AT.js settings, the Code Settings option will let you place custom Javascript code where?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Library Header only","Library Footer only","Library Header & Footer","Directly inside the global-mbox","Appended to the bottom of the AT.js file"],"correct_options":["Library Header & Footer"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you are not using a Tag Management System, How do you implement AT.JS on your site?","presented_options":["Download AT.JS and include a reference to AT.jS in the script tag within the page Head section","Download AT.JS and include a reference to AT.jS in the script tag within the page Footer","Download AT.JS and include a reference to AT.jS in the script tag within the page Body section","No need to reference on your site as Target does this for you"],"correct_options":["Download AT.JS and include a reference to AT.jS in the script tag within the page Head section"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where do you go to download or edit the mbox.js or at.js settings within Adobe Target?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Setup > Downloads","Setup > Tag Management","Setup > Implementation","Profile > Setup","System > Configuraiton"],"correct_options":["Setup > Implementation"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In Adobe Target's mbox.js Edit settings, selecting which Compression Level option will minify the file and decrease the page load time and improve the end user experience?","presented_options":["weak compression","no compression","fast compression","max minification"],"correct_options":["strong compression"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When using mbox.js, Code settings can be applied to which areas ?","presented_options":["mboxSupported() function body","mboxCookieDomain() function body","Extra Javascript","mboxParameters(), mboxSupported(), mboxCookieDomain() function bodies and Extra Javascript"],"correct_options":["mboxParameters(), mboxSupported(), mboxCookieDomain() function bodies and Extra Javascript"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Implementation Models and Platforms Overview: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of your browser's developer tool sections can be used for output of logging statements, executing Javascript commands that allow you to interact with Target and your site ?","presented_options":["Console","Timeline","Courses","Network"],"correct_options":["Console"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"While debugging an mbox request, where would you go to see a list of name value pairs that were sent to Target as part of the mbox call?","presented_options":["Browser's dev tools > Network tab  > Filter on mbox &  look in mbox.s or at.js contents file","Browser's dev tools > Network tab  > Filter on mbox & click on server call then look in Query string parameters listed within the headers tab","Log into Adobe Target Marketing Cloud > Debug Section","Adobe Target Activity > Debug Tab"],"correct_options":["Browser's dev tools > Network tab  > Filter on mbox & click on server call then look in Query string parameters listed within the headers tab"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"While debugging an mbox request, where would you go to see the content offer returned from Adobe Target for a mbox call?","presented_options":["Browser's dev tools > Network tab  > Filter on mbox & click on server call then look at the Response Tab to view the contents","Log into Adobe Target Marketing Cloud > Debug Section","Adobe Target Activity > Debug Tab"],"correct_options":["Browser's dev tools > Network tab  > Filter on mbox & click on server call then look at the Response Tab to view the contents"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How would you enable the debug logging details to the browser console of the following types of information: hiding elements before applying actions, preparing to apply an action, and seeing content to apply/swap on the page?","presented_options":["Add Parameter mboxDebug=Console to page URL","Add VECOfferDebug=Console to page URL","Select VEC Offer Debugging in Marketing Cloud Debugger and refresh page","In Adobe Target Activty set VEC Offer Debug to True"],"correct_options":["Select VEC Offer Debugging in Marketing Cloud Debugger and refresh page"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"While using the VEC Offer Debugging option,  a log entry of 'Allowed Unsuccesfull Polling Attempts Reached' is an indication that: ","presented_options":["The Social media polling activity is not active","There was an attemtp to change page content, but Target was unable to locate the content area on the page","mBox call was unable to reach Adobe Target","The page request time exceeded the allowed polling time"],"correct_options":["There was an attemtp to change page content, but Target was unable to locate the content area on the page"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When you're using mboxTrace for Troubleshooting, which parameter prints into a popup window as a JSON String?","presented_options":["?mboxTrace=json","?mboxtTrace=console","?mboxTrace=window","?mboxTrace=print"],"correct_options":["?mboxTrace=window"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A debugging Authentication Token that is used to allow only authorized users debugging ability -  is by default set to expire after how long?  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["1 day","1 hour","6 hours","12 hours","1 week"],"correct_options":["6 hours"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In order to see how Target profile scripts are modfying calling user's profile attributes, you can use what?","presented_options":["mBoxTrace options","Target Activity Debug Mode","Adobe.io Degubber","Visual Experience Debugger","Target Premium Enhanced Debugging"],"correct_options":["mboxTrace options"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which option below is a plugin and troubleshooting method devleoped by Adobe Target Professional Services that uses a token replacement process to expose Acitivy & Experience details in a Page level Javascript variable.","presented_options":["ttDebug","ttAdBox","ttMETA","ttActDebug"],"correct_options":["ttMETA"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"In order to turn off debug tracing session mode, you would pass the following URL parameters to the page: '?mboxTrace=off' TRUE or FALSE","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Target Echnical Foundations: Activity Troubleshooting: Tools for Troubleshooting Target CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"MVT Reporting counting methodology per activity report can be set to :  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Orders, Visits","Visitors, Visits, or Activity Impressions","Lifetime Value, Orders, Visits","Activity Impressions, Orders"],"correct_options":["Visitors, Visits, or Activity Impressions"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: MVT Reporting : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"MVT Reporting Dimensions can be set to : Select the four correct Answers:","presented_options":["Revenue per Visitor(RPV)","Order Rate","Impressions","Average Order Value(AOV)","Total Sales","Visits"],"correct_options":["Revenue per Visitor(RPV)","Order Rate","Average Order Value(AOV)","Total Sales"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: MVT Reporting : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This MVT Report shows how much influence each unique  location had on the most conversions.  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["Value Based Report(VBR)","Location Based Report(LBR)","Influence Report","Offer Level report"],"correct_options":["Influence Report"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: MVT Reporting : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Offer level reporting has offer by location including Lift, Confidence and Revenue Per Visitor.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: MVT Reporting : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you setup an MVT activity with 3 Experiences in 3 Locations, how many unique experiences will be setup by default?","presented_options":["3","9","6","12","27"],"correct_options":["27"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: MVT Reporting : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Traffic Estimator is avaialble for the following types of Target Activities:Select the correct answer","presented_options":["All Target Activities","MVT Activities","MVT & Auto Personalization Activities","Auto Target & Auto Personalization"],"correct_options":["MVT & Auto Personalization Activities"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Traffic Estimator : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What tool/utility has additional functionality compared to the traffic estimator and is independent of the interface and stored on a separate URL?","presented_options":["The Traffic Calculator","TrafficEstimator.com","EstimateMyTraffic.com","Auto-Traffic-ML"],"correct_options":["The Traffic Calculator"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Traffic Estimator : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"In order to determine if you MVT Activity will get enough traffic for the number of Content Contributions, what pieces of data must you enter?Select all that apply","presented_options":["Typical Conversion Rate","Estimated Activity Impressions per Day","Test Duration","Number of Sessions","Audience Size","Number of Offer Contributions"],"correct_options":["Typical Conversion Rate","Estimated Activity Impressions per Day","Test Duration"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Traffic Estimator : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The 'Bonferroni Correction' is a more conservative view of statistical data to see how long the test will take.  This will ensure the data is as accurate as possible.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Traffic Estimator : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The RPV Metric can be seen within the Traffic Estimator Tool.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng: Traffic Estimator : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you want to have the ability to select any Anaytics Metric for reporting and add new segments and apply results retroactively to the test, you should be using what?","presented_options":["A4T.js","AT.js","mbox.js","Target Premium","Adobe.io"],"correct_options":["A4T.js"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng:Analytics for Target(A4T) : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When using Analytics as your reporting source for an activity, you must select the audience setup when setting up the Primary Goal.  True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng:Analytics for Target(A4T) : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"To ensure there is no data variance between Target and Analytics,  Optimization data is flowing from Target to Analytics on every call to Target from your visitors. This is done how?","presented_options":["From the servers directly and not through calls on the visitors web page","From the clients browser directly and not through calls on servers","Manually","In the Target/Analtyics scheduled batch process","The first line in Javascript in the Head section of the page"],"correct_options":["From the servers directly and not through calls on the visitors web page"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng:Analytics for Target(A4T) : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A pre-requisite to using A4T is to be on what?","presented_options":["Analytics Regional Data Collection","Analytics Global Data Collection","Target Premium","The Latest version of Adobe Target","AWS - Amazon Web Services"],"correct_options":["Analytics Regional Data Collection"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Techincal Foundations (OD) Activity Reporitng:Analytics for Target(A4T) : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"____  let you automatically output Target-specific information (campaign details, user profile information, geo information, and so forth) to use in debugging or integrating with 3rd-party systems (such as Clicktale).   ____ let you choose which variables to leverage and then enable them to be sent as part of an mbox response. In order to do so, you simply enable a variable using the switch and the variable will be sent with mbox responses, which can be validated in network calls.    Fill in the blank","presented_options":["Response Tokens","Cookies","mBox Parameters","Global Variables"],"correct_options":["Response Tokens"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The estimated lift is calculated using the following formula:  Select the correct answer","presented_options":["(<winning experience RPV> - <control experience RPV<)*<total number of visitors in the activity>","<winning experience RPV> * <total number of visitors in the activity>","<winning experience RPV> / <total number of visitors in the activity>","<control experience RPV> * <total number of visitors in the activity>"],"correct_options":["(<winning experience RPV> - <control experience RPV<)*<total number of visitors in the activity>"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Account Settings Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What are some reasons the Esimated Lift in Revenue is not being shown on the activities page, even though it has been enabled?","presented_options":["There were not enough visitors to calculate the value","You did not provide an estimated value metric in the goals and settings page when setting up the activity","The best performing experience is the control experience","You are running Target Standard and this feature requires Target Premium","Estimated Lift is only availabe fo winning Product Recommendations"],"correct_options":["There were not enough visitors to calculate the value","You did not provide an estimated value metric in the goals and settings page when setting up the activity","The best performing experience is the control experience"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Account Settings Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you turn off the use of element IDs for generating CSS Selectors to locate items on the page, target will then default to finding elements by using?","presented_options":["Javascript functions","Auto-Targeting","regex","Element CSS Classes"],"correct_options":["Element CSS Classes"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Account Settings Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In order to display an image of your experience on the flow diagram of the activity, you should enable which feature under the Visual Experience Composer Settings?","presented_options":["Generate Experience Snapshots","Dynamic Image Capture","Target Snaphot Service","#Target Activity Selfie"],"correct_options":["Generate Experience Snapshots"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Account Settings Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In order to preview how your activity will look on different size mobile devices within the Visual Experience Composer, you should add devices within this section of the Account Preferences.  ","presented_options":["Mobile Viewport Configuration","Mobile Devices","Phablet Settings","Mobile Device Setup","Target Devices Configuration"],"correct_options":["Mobile Viewport Configuration"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Account Settings Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When using Experience Targeting, if a visitor has been shown mulitple experiences for an activity and coverts.  The conversion is attributed to ?","presented_options":["The last viewed Experience","The first viewed Experience","The most viewed Experience","A random experience","The expereince leading to a sale"],"correct_options":["The last viewed Experience"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Experience Targeting Tests: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When using Experience Targeting, A Visitor is counted for ?","presented_options":["Each experience they see","The last Experience they see","The first experience they see","The experience where the visitor spent the most time"],"correct_options":["Each experience they see"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Experience Targeting Tests: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When using Experience Targeting, if a visitor qualifies for more than one experience within an activity, what is the evaluation criteria used to determine which experience they are shown?","presented_options":["Bottom-Up","Random Selection","Most Viewed","Winning Experience","Top-Down"],"correct_options":["Top-Down"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Experience Targeting Tests: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you setup an MVT activity with 3 variations of the marquee image, 2 variations of the header text, and 4 variations of a CTA button.  How many distinct offer combinations will be setup for the actiivty?","presented_options":["24","9","10","14","18"],"correct_options":["24"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Creating a multivariate test - CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"One advantage of using this type of test instead of an A/B test is that the this test will show which element most contributes to a campains success.  What is this type of test?","presented_options":["MVT","Enhanced Targeting","Auto Personalization","Element Optimization","Recommendations"],"correct_options":["MVT"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Creating a multivariate test - CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"When executing an MVT Test, test duration will be impacted by: ","presented_options":["Number of elements","Number of locations","Number of experiences","Number of conversions","Number of other activities running","Number of collisions"],"correct_options":["Number of elements","Number of locations"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Creating a multivariate test - CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What two reports are available when you analyze the results of you multivariate Test?","presented_options":["Experience Peformance Report","Location Contribution Report","Offer Contribution Report","Converion Report","Location-Offer Report"],"correct_options":["Experience Peformance Report","Location Contribution Report"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Creating a multivariate test - CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where does in Adobe Target can you see the Collision Report?","presented_options":["Within each activity on Collision Tab","Within each activity on the Reporting tab","Under Settings - Collision Reporting","Only present within MVT Activities"],"correct_options":["Within each activity on Collision Tab"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical Foundations OD) Collision Detection:CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"An Activity collision by definition Is when ?","presented_options":["When two or more activities have been configured for the same page URL","When two or more activities have been configured for the same audience","When two or more of the same type of activities have been configured for the same page URL","When two or more activities have been configured for the same date and time"],"correct_options":["When two or more activities have been configured for the same page URL"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical Foundations OD) Collision Detection:CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When Adobe Target delivers content to the page, the activities are rendered in what order?","presented_options":["Reverse Priority Order","Priority Order","Alphabetical Ordre","Top Down Order"],"correct_options":["Reverse Priority Order"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical Foundations OD) Collision Detection:CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The Collision Report shows potential collsions as opposed to actual collisions.  Ture or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical Foundations OD) Collision Detection:CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When using Auto-Allocate for A/B Tests, existing visitors will always see the leading experience even if it is different than their assigned experience. True or False","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Auto-Allocate tests : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When you want to optimize your activity from the beginning and identify the winning experiences as quickly as possible, you should select which type of activity?","presented_options":["Auto-Allocate","A/B Tests","Automated Personalization"],"correct_options":["Auto-Allocate"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Auto-Allocate tests : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When you want to characterize/rank the performance of all experiences before optimizing your site, you should select which type of activity?","presented_options":["Auto-Allocate","A/B Tests","Automated Personalization"],"correct_options":["A/B Tests"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Auto-Allocate tests : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When you want to have the following: Optimize combinations of content, not pre=defined experiences.Complex optimization algorithms that build predictions based on individual profiles.Discover responsive visitor segments.  You should select which type of activity?","presented_options":["Auto-Allocate","A/B Tests","Automated Personalization"],"correct_options":["Automated Personalization"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Auto-Allocate tests : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If the legacy priority settings of Low, Medium, and High are not enough when asisgning the priority settings, enabling Fine-grained priorites allow you to set priorties on a scale from ?","presented_options":["0 to 999","0 to 10","Low, Medium, High,Critical","1-100"],"correct_options":["0 to 999"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Activity Settings : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you create a 4-way Auto Allocate test, for which all 4 Experiences are identical. Once sufficient traffic has been reached so the algorithm has enough data so it can perform allocation what would you expect to see as a result?","presented_options":["Traffic remains equally distrubuted across the 4 options","One Experience will receive 100% of the traffic","One Experience will receive 70% of the traffic and 30% will be randomly distributed to the other three"],"correct_options":["Traffic remains equally distrubuted across the 4 options"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Auto-Allocate tests : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What are the two types of audiences within Adobe Target?","presented_options":["Targeting Audiences","Reporting Audiences","Active Audiences","Inactive Audiences","Mobile Audiences","Web Audiences"],"correct_options":["Targeting Audiences","Reporting Audiences"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations(OD) Using Audiences: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"_____ help you deliver different content to different type of visitors","presented_options":["Targeting Audiences","Reporting Audiences","Active Audiences","Inactive Audiences","Mobile Audiences","Web Audiences"],"correct_options":["Targeting Audiences"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations(OD) Using Audiences: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"_____ help you determine how different types of visitors respond to the same content","presented_options":["Targeting Audiences","Reporting Audiences","Active Audiences","Inactive Audiences","Mobile Audiences","Web Audiences"],"correct_options":["Reporting Audiences"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations(OD) Using Audiences: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What options are available when combining rules and parameters for audience definitions?","presented_options":["AND","OR","IN","OUT","INLCUDE","EXCLUDE"],"correct_options":["AND","OR"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations(OD) Creating Audiences: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When creating an audience within Target, if you want to utilize a parameter coming from the mBox, which Rule option would you need to use","presented_options":["Custom","Network","Target Library","Site Pages","Traffic Sources"],"correct_options":["Custom"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations(OD) Creating Audiences: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When creating an audience within Target, if you want to target new or returning visitors, which Rule option would you need to use","presented_options":["Visitor Profile","Custom","Network","Target Library","Site Pages"],"correct_options":["Visitor Profile"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations(OD) Creating Audiences: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When creating an audience within Target, if you want to target visitors based on what sites there were coming from when landing on your site, which Rule Option would you need to use?","presented_options":["Traffic Sources","Custom","Network","Target Library","Site Pages"],"correct_options":["Traffic Sources"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations(OD) Creating Audiences: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"By Default when setting up an activity, the start/end dates are set to?","presented_options":["When Activated / When Deactivated","Now / Never","When Activated / Never","Now / When Deactivated"],"correct_options":["When Activated / When Deactivated"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Activity Settings : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What are the three type of 'Goal' metrics ?","presented_options":["Conversion","Revenue","Engagement","Orders","Visits","Visitors"],"correct_options":["Conversion","Revenue","Engagement"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Activity Metrics : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"When setting up an activty and selecting a goal metric of Engagement, if you wanted to assign different engagement weights to different pages to show that some pages have a higher value in relation to the test.  What actions should you take?","presented_options":["Select Custom Scoring as Secondary metric","Pass in custom Scoring value to the mBox as a parameter","Select Site Pages as Secondary metric","Assign Custom weights within Goal Metric Section"],"correct_options":["Select Custom Scoring as Secondary metric","Pass in custom Scoring value to the mBox as a parameter"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Activity Metrics : CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"______ is a code snippet defined in Target that uses server-side JavaScript to capture visitor attribute","presented_options":["Profile Script","Profile Parameters","Adobe.io script","Server Side API","Visitor API"],"correct_options":["Profile Script"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Profile Scripts: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"______ capture visitor attributes by passing attributes values up thorugh mBox calls in the code implementation of Target(mBox.js or AT.js)","presented_options":["Profile Parameters","Profile Script","Adobe.io script","Visitor API","Server SideAPI"],"correct_options":["Profile Parameters"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Profile Scripts: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What three user encounter settings are available within Activity Metrics?","presented_options":["Increment Count & Keep User in Activity","Increment Count & Release User & Allow Reentry","Increment Count & Release User & Bar Reentry","Increment Count & Exclude User from Activity","Increment Count & Release User"],"correct_options":["Increment Count & Keep User in Activity","Increment Count & Release User & Allow Reentry","Increment Count & Release User & Bar Reentry"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Advanced Metrics: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you want to use the Advanced Activity Metrics settings for an Activity, you must select what as the Reporting Source?","presented_options":["Adobe Target","Adobe Anaytics","Either Adobe Target or Adobe Analytics","The exact location within the experience"],"correct_options":["Adobe Target"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Advanced Metrics: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Adobe Target provides the following Qaulity Assurance Options:  ","presented_options":["VEC, during Authoring","Preview Links","Targeted Audience to Limit Entry","Host Groups","Automated Test Scripts","mBox parameter IsQAMode"],"correct_options":["VEC, during Authoring","Preview Links","Targeted Audience to Limit Entry","Host Groups"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Quality Assurance and Activation: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This Target Quality Assurance Option offers the following Benefits: Content renders precisely as it will in the final activityEasy to Qualify  - can force an active entryGreat for Browser Compatability TestsEasy to share with team members without Target Login","presented_options":["Preview Links","VEC","Targeted Audience","Host Groups"],"correct_options":["Preview Links"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Quality Assurance and Activation: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This Target Quality Assurance Option offers the following Benefits: Content renders precisely as it will in the final activityTargeting conditions can be testedSuccess metrics(reporting) can be testedAllows testing in productionAllows testing of delivery timing from target","presented_options":["Preview Links","VEC","Targeted Audience","Host Groups"],"correct_options":["Targeted Audience"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Quality Assurance and Activation: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This Target Quality Assurance Option offers the following Benefits: Content renders precisely as it will in the final,published activity(assuming test and prod environments)Targeting conditions can be testedSuccess metrics(reporting) can be testedAllows testing in productionCan avoid Data Pollution","presented_options":["Preview Links","VEC","Targeted Audience","Host Groups"],"correct_options":["Host Groups"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Target Technical foundations (OD) Quality Assurance and Activation: CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which activity type should be used to deliver a temporary promotion banner to all site visitors that clicked through an email campaign?","presented_options":["Experience Targeting","A/B Test","Automated Personalization","Recommendations"],"correct_options":["Experience Targeting"],"exam_topics":["Planning and Configuring"],"question_source":"Business Practitioner Sample Exam Test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A Target Business Practitioner (BP) needs to create an activity. The Target BP chooses AdobeTarget as a reporting source instead of Adobe Analytics.What is one reason that the Target BP chooses Adobe Target?","presented_options":["The BP wants to create multiple custom metrics using the VEC.","Adobe Analytics causes a 24-hour delay in results.","An unusually high number of visitors must be tracked in the activity.","Analysis needs to include trends over time."],"correct_options":["The BP wants to create multiple custom metrics using the VEC."],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Business Practitioner Sample Exam Test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A Target Business Practitioner needs to make sure an activity is free of any collisions with any previously made activities.How should the Target Business Practitioner confirm that this is true?","presented_options":["Launch the activity and rely on Target to block any colliding activities.","Review the Status, Priority, and Audience of every activity on the same URL to make sure there is no undesired overlap.","Confirm that the activity has a unique name that is NOT duplicated or closely resembled elsewhere.","Set the priority level to \"high\" on the new activity."],"correct_options":["Review the Status, Priority, and Audience of every activity on the same URL to make sure there is no undesired overlap."],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Business Practitioner Sample Exam Test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A stakeholder asks the Target Business Practitioner (BP) to create an activity that tests the addition of a pop-up message after a visitor adds an item to their cart.Which of the following would allow the BP to correctly target this audience?","presented_options":["Add a custom mbox parameter for users with cart additions and target this audience to users with that parameter","Create an Analytics segment published to the Marketing Cloud for visitors with cart additions and target this audience to that segment","Select Visitor Profile > \"Cart Additions\" in audience creation","Target the activity to the cart URL"],"correct_options":["Add a custom mbox parameter for users with cart additions and target this audience to users with that parameter"],"exam_topics":["Executing and Managing"],"question_source":"Business Practitioner Sample Exam Test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A particular search engine marketing campaign is driving users to a landing page URL with tracking codes appended. The tracking codes must be present in the URL for the search team's tracking, which occurs in a separate tool. A Target Business Practitioner (BP) created an activity experience that redirects incoming users from that default landing page to a new page. After the activity has been running for 1 week, the search team notes that the tracking codes are NOT included in the URL when users arrive at the new page. What should the BP do to fix this?","presented_options":["Create a profile script that will store the tracking codes for each user","Change the activity to exclude users without a tracking code","Include the new page in the activity URL targeting","Check the \"Include Current Query Parameters\" checkbox on the experience"],"correct_options":["Check the \"Include Current Query Parameters\" checkbox on the experience"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Business Practitioner Sample Exam Test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A Target Business Practitioner (BP) reviews the ongoing results of an activity with four experiences. The BP notes that there are about 400-500 visitors for each experience, but the clickthrough metric shows 0 for two of the experiences. Which step should the BP take first?","presented_options":["Verify the metric is set up properly in the activity","Remove any activity experiences with data discrepancies","Pause and restart the activity","Stop the test and report on all current findings"],"correct_options":["Verify the metric is set up properly in the activity"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Business Practitioner Sample Exam Test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The conversion rate in the results data for an A/B Test activity is much lower than expected. A Target Business Practitioner (BP) must validate the ongoing activity and ensure proper performance. What should the BP do first?","presented_options":["Monitor data of all live activities","End the activity immediately","Re-examine the activity setup and metrics","Reduce traffic exposure to 50%"],"correct_options":["Re-examine the activity setup and metrics"],"exam_topics":["Troubleshooting"],"question_source":"Business Practitioner Sample Exam Test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A Target Business Practitioner (BP) is reviewing test results after an activity has ended. The test showed a 5% increase in revenue per visitor. The sample size was reached, which was set to prove up to a 2% difference in order rate.The following effects were observed:• 5% increase in revenue per visitor (RPV)• 0.5% increase in orders per visitor• 3% increase in average order value• 3.5% increase in average order size• 0.5% decrease in page views• 0.8% increase in product viewsA stakeholder asks the BP to annualize the impact on revenue projected through the next year to present as program ROI.How should the BP proceed?","presented_options":["Inform the stakeholder that the result would NOT be trustworthy because the test was sized to prove differences in order rate.","Project annual revenue attributed to the audience in the test over the next year and multiply by the lift observed.","Project annual revenue attributed to the audience in the test over the next year and multiply by the lift observed.","Inform the stakeholder that the test would need to run four times as long to prove differences in order rate."],"correct_options":["Inform the stakeholder that the result would NOT be trustworthy because the test was sized to prove differences in order rate."],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Business Practitioner Sample Exam Test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When viewing the Location Contribution Report, which table shows conversion rate, lift and confidence for each offer?  Select the correct ansewr","presented_options":["Offer-Level","Influence","Summary","Primary"],"correct_options":["Offer-Level"],"exam_topics":["Analyzing and Reporting"],"question_source":"Target Activity : test OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      } 
      
  ]
}